Y-You're kidding me...
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 3
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Enjoys a Day Off
I'm so tired.
My legs can't take this anymore...
An animal howl?
A monster?
But I've never seen anything
like that before.
It's abnormally sturdy.
What the hell is that thing?!
Maybe just for a moment—
Evi!
Elisa!
Ray!
Yeah!
What on earth is this monster?
That was incredible, Ray!
You split that monster clean open.
Elisa.
Are you all right?
I was so scared!
There, there.
You did well.
This was thanks to you.
Hey, Al.
That withered... I mean, White.
Maybe he's actually legit?
Let's go.
Hey, Al!
I'm not yet— Hey!
Is this for real?
Ray was actually that strong?!
And stamp!
And now we've got them all.
We did it.
I'm really sorry for getting
in everyone's way.
You really didn't.
A practical exercise in this forest was
already pretty rough for students.
On top of that, Evi and I
train our bodies every day,
and we forced you to keep up with our pace.
If anything, it's the two of us
who should be apologizing.
That's right.
Sorry about that.
Not at all.
Thank you, everyone.
Elisa, you're just too adorable.
Ray, you didn't even flinch.
No, this too—
That backwoods forest training, right?
Right.
Um, Amelia, that kind of tickles.
Um...
And the top score for this
practical exercise goes to...
Amelia Rose's group!
Wow. Tough crowd.
That's just like Lady Amelia!
Oh, so noble.
Eww! Why is that withered next to her?!
So gross!
Really, he's disgusting!
I mean, they only won because of Amelia.
Obviously.
Otherwise someone like that wouldn't have a
chance to stand in front of us aristocrats!
That's right!
They're not really cheering for us, huh?
Looks that way.
I guess everybody's not
happy to see me up here.
You don't need to let that bother you.
She's right.
It doesn't change the fact that we got the best score.
Withered...
Typical aristocrats.
That is exactly what I mean.
Amelia?
It's too soon, you know?
Not yet.
Ugh, I know!
But it's been two months!
Three days is enough for a young boy
to become a totally new person!
And it's been twenty times that.
Twenty times!
It looks like he's here.
He is?
I will go get him.
Please do.
It's been a long time, Master Ray.
It really has, Carla.
Well, then. Lady Lydia is waiting for you.
Excuse me.
Ray, is that you?
It's been a while.
Have you grown?
I don't think so, Master.
I see.
But I guess these days,
I'm the one looking up at you.
It didn't used to be like that.
Why don't you take a seat?
Are you doing well?
I am.
But of course...
I see.
So that's not there yet.
I estimate that it'll take
about five years or so.
Of course—
Using it is
strictly forbidden, right?
That's right.
However, if you ever feel like you absolutely need it,
you'll have to make the call.
After all, I did pass the mantle
of "Iceblade Sorcerer" to you.
Anyway, I called you here today
in regards to a rumor spreading
among the sorcery researchers.
A rumor?
Is that really something you
need to concern yourself with?
It is.
I wouldn't bother myself
with some petty rumor,
but Engram is another matter all together.
Engram?
Normally, when we talk
about sorcery research,
we focus on sorcery itself,
that is to say, the code, right?
That is right.
But what I'm researching
is something different.
So then, what are you researching?
This.
The head? No, the brain?
Yes.
You do know that sorcery
begins in the brain, right?
I do.
The frontal lobe of the brain
processes the internal information
format according to code theory.
It materializes when it comes into
contact with the Prima materia.
That is the sorcery we utilize.
Right.
By directing my attention to the brain,
I discovered the twofold code theory.
Announcing this has triggered
an entirely new movement.
Now, sorcery research and the brain
are in a close relationship.
I see.
The part of the brain where memories
of sorcery are stored is...
Engram.
Exactly.
Researching the brain might lead
to decoding sorcery itself,
actually, maybe even to the
truth about our entire world.
Did you say that researching
the brain and sorcery
will lead to decoding
the truth of the world?
Isn't that an exciting prospect?
But then they always appear.
The people who will do anything
to get what they want.
What is that?
Instead of spending time to
analyze the brain using sorcery,
these people cut open sorcerers' brains
to rummage around inside.
They have no qualms about crossing the
line that humanity must not cross.
Those delusional pieces of trash
call themselves "Eugenics".
Eugenics...
They wanted me to join them.
Those idiots believed I'd say yes.
According to Carol,
they've begun contacting other
prominent sorcerers, as well.
If you do not have human dignity,
you cannot advance sorcery.
Ray, you understand that, right?
Yes, I do.
As I would expect from my star pupil.
It's so nice to take a walk in the forest!
Especially after a depressing
talk like that.
Having you here like this brings
back memories of our training days.
You mean the Ainsworth-style boot camp.
That brings back memories.
That made even the military's elite give up,
but you finished it as a child.
That was the only thing I was good at.
Ray, you've made some friends, haven't you?
Yes.
I've made some wonderful friends
since entering the academy,
including a half-elf girl who
absolutely loves your books.
I want you to bring them next time.
Sure. I didn't think you'd be so excited.
I mean, your smile was a lot stiffer
before you entered the academy.
Of course I want to meet the people
who have softened your smile.
Master...
It's almost June.
The Magic Chevalier will be starting soon.
That's the magic sword-fighting competition
held between the kingdom's three
sorcery academies, right?
Yes.
Incidentally, I've won four times in a row.
If you entered it, I'm sure you'd
also be able to win four in a row.
I think I'd rather stay
more in the background.
Of course one reason is my recuperation,
but I also want to cheer on my friends.
Please do as you like.
After all...
Now that I am like this,
I no longer have the power to protect you.
That's not true.
Seeing you has reassured me, though.
I'll pass this on to you.
I'm sure it will be of use to you someday.
Thank you very much.
That's a version adapted
specifically for a student.
Really?
I figured it might come in handy.
You really are amazing.
Again.
Huh?
Praise me again.
You really are amazing.
That's so good. Again!
Oh, hey, Elisa.
Good morning, Ray.
Good morning.
Are you going somewhere?
I was thinking I'd go visit the library and
the bookstore in the Middle District today.
That sounds great.
Do you mind if I come along?
I'm sorry I made you wait.
I hope this is all right.
I think you look really cute.
Of course the pure white dress is nice,
but I especially like your hair like that.
It really accentuates your beauty.
Th-Thank you!
You're also...
Y-You're also looking great!
Thank you.
But anyway, why did you change clothes?
Well, since... we're going
somewhere together.
I see.
That makes sense.
You like to look nice, huh Elisa?
Thank you!
This is...
These are Dr. Ainsworth's early
notes on her sorcery research.
You really like her, huh?
I do! I really like her revolutionary
thinking that focuses on Engram.
This book's release kicked off an entirely
new movement in sorcery research!
What are you reading?
It's a novel about love.
This is one of Luna Ether's works.
What?!
I-I'm sorry.
Is that strange?
I guess so.
You can accurately feel the nuances of
peoples' emotions when you read novels like these.
I feel like this author is
especially good at depicting them.
Because I don't know these things,
I'm really drawn to learning about them.
I see.
Well, I think that's really great, Ray.
What? I would've never expected
to run into Ray at the library.
And with another girl, too.
Why is approaching him so hard?
I just have to walk up with a
smile and it won't be a problem.
That's what it said in that
book I read the other day.
I see you're studying hard, Claris.
That's right!
I am of noble blood, after all.
I wasn't expecting to run into you here.
What?
Well, that, that's just...
We're going to get some lunch now.
Would you like to join us?
So what you mean is that you'd
like for me to join you for lunch?
That's right.
I don't have a choice, do I?
I don't have a choice,
so I'll do you a favor and join.
Let me introduce you.
This sweet angel is Elisa.
She's got an exceptionally beautiful heart,
excels at being considerate in subtle ways,
studies hard, and is vastly knowledgeable.
Uh, my name is Elisa Griffith.
It's so nice to meet you!
And then this one-of-a-kind lady who loves
and is loved by these transcendentally
wavy twintails is Claris.
She has the highest level of elegance,
with which she expertly weaves
I—
Um, that's...
perfect sweetness into
her otherwise cool demeanor.
My name is C-Claris Cleveland.
I've never done this kind of thing before...
I mean...
Me, neither.
Uh, the weather.
The weather is so nice today!
I-It really is!
This is so delicious.
It really is.
It's... nice to spend our day off together.
That is spot-on, um, Elisa.
Thank you, Claris.
Thank you for coming today, Ray.
See you in school.
All right.
I can't believe your dad's also an Ainger.
Ray!
What a surprise, running into you here.
The nobles had a gathering of sorts today.
It really gets so tiring.
Now that we're getting closer
to the Magic Chevalier,
these meet and greets are only
going to get more frequent.
Oh, I'm really sorry for venting like that.
I don't mind.
I'm sure you need to get it
off your chest sometimes.
Ray...
And then,
that formal outfit, which is distinctly different
from our uniform, suits you incredibly well.
It really accentuates your beauty and wisdom.
Thank you.
Speaking of, what have you been up to today?
Actually...
Hmm...
So you had lunch with Elisa and the
daughter of the Cleveland family?
I'm sure you had a lot of fun.
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
Hey! Will you go somewhere with me right now?
You have time, right?
I don't mind.
Wow, that looks so feminine and beautiful!
So cute! My heart is tingling.
Very cool. So cool it's hot.
You are a veritable Rose of Passion.
I've pricked my heart!
You know, I was thinking this before, too,
but you certainly seem at ease with girls.
Really? I guess I never really
thought about myself that way,
but I grew up in an environment
with a lot of women.
Is that how that works?
Well, either way, that's...
I want wings.
What's wrong, Amelia?
Amelia?
It's a... a... It's....
I'm so sorry!
This is too embarrassing.
Amelia, are you all right?
I, uh, yes!
I'm sorry.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
I carelessly touched your bare skin.
Huh? Oh, that's not an issue.
I see.
Maybe I could show Ray who I really am, someday...
I'm sorry to have summoned
you so suddenly.
No, it's perfectly fine.
You don't have to be so formal.
This isn't the military.
I apologize.
White, how are you finding
life as a student?
I'm finding it extremely satisfying.
Is that so?
Did something happen?
No. In all honesty, I was simply worried.
You're the first ordinary to enter
the academy since its inception.
The noble-born students must
be giving you a lot of grief.
I'm sorry.
As aware of it as I am,
there is nothing I can
presently do about it.
It's not a problem at all.
I'm painfully aware of it myself.
Despite the fact that several years have passed
since becoming a teacher at this academy,
I've still been trying to
be a sorcery researcher.
We get them every year.
Whether it's due to relationships or grades,
they feel like they're not going to make it here,
and end up leaving the academy heartbroken.
All of them students who would have had
the chance to become excellent sorcerers.
I should have paid more attention.
I should have approached them more.
I should have been a teacher who spent her life helping students
instead of being some aloof researcher.
Professor Gray...
Sorry for being self-centered.
This is my ego showing.
But right now, I very strongly
want to be your teacher.
You are my teacher, Professor Gray.
Does the teacher make the student,
or does the student make the teacher?
At any rate, please come to me
if you're having any problems.
Thank you very much.
I am very lucky.
I am blessed with both friends and teachers.
Thank you, Ray White.
Al hasn't come back to
school since then, has he?
I haven't seen him, either.
Where is he?
Just you wait, Ray White!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
Um, this is the preview
for the next episode of
"The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World".
While Ray is living
the peaceful academy life,
a ferocious blade hounds him
relentlessly and won't let up!
A duel begins!
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Releases His Secret Power!"
Episode 4
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Releases His Secret Power
Um, this was Elisa Griffith.